♪From primal chaos to the starry sky♪
♪In the whole world,
we shall hold the balance♪
♪The cauldron tempers divine blades♪
♪The furnace refines the empty void♪
♪The Way is in mystic fate♪
♪Be brave enough
to split the primal chaos wide open♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel
by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
[Episode 11]
Without power,
you'd set such a thorough trap.
Why attack when you can ambush?
Why use powers when you can poison?
What's with that disgusted look?
Too bad all your effort
won't work on the locals.
Didn't you say they know no spells?
More than that.
They're...
Forget it.
You'll see when you meet them.
Here they come.
Why won't the doors open?
You're awake.
See?
What do you mean?
Now you know
I put you here to heal.
Heal?
You call that healing?
This woodshed
is the coziest spot in Bear Stockade.
Warm and quiet.
You don't like it?
Then what's with the shackles?
Feared you'd roll around
and hurt yourselves more.
Seeing your skinny limbs,
I used lighter chains.
Otherwise, our dog chains
are way thicker than these.
Thanks for your care.
Don't mention it.
We'll never forget this.
Bye.
You are leaving?
Didn't you say to heal?
My injury's healed.
I don't know about her,
but I'm fine.
Can I leave first?
Why leave?
Bear Stockade
is the world's
most wonderful place.
Nobody who comes wants to leave.
Lady,
pardon my frankness.
This place,
though not a harsh land,
it's still a desolate wilderness.
No aura above, no essence below.
You can't grow crops
or achieve greatness.
The two of us
left our homes.
Every night
I think of my homeland,
and my heart gets...
We're staying.
Really?
Told you.
Bear Stockade is the best.
Nobody wants to leave.
I'll show you around.
Come on.
No dawdling now.
Move along.
On Bear Island,
only beasts work till they drop.
No fallow field is ruined by tilling.
Bear Island has comfy weather
and fresh air.
Look at everyone working.
So at ease, so joyful.
Seriously?
It really breeds uniqueness.
Fits the name.
The Dragon King didn't lie.
The Pregenesis Sword
is indeed here.
How did you know?
The Pregenesis Sword
was made by Ancestral Witch heirs.
Legend says after the ancient war,
they guarded it until today.
Ancestral Witch heirs?
Forgot to introduce.
This is my brother, Xiong Da.
Greetings.
This is my other brother, Xiong Er.
Let me guess.
Xiong San, right?
You fool.
My sister is Xiong Lingli.
Guessing wrong on that.
Are you an idiot?
You chose the right boss.
Lingli
is Chief's precious jewel
and our village's
wild beauty.
Brother.
You're embarrassing me.
Stop it.
He said it. Why hit me?
Look how skinny they are.
Yeah.
Outside world must be tough.
You must be starving.
Don't worry.
Good times start on Bear Island.
No more hardship from now on.
Everyone who came here
has never left.
Yeah.
No one's ever left.
No one
has left?
Then I...
It's time.
Bear Island is so great.
We love Bear Island.
Listen to the deity.
And we'll live forever.
Bear Island is so great.
We love Bear Island.
Listen to the deity.
- I see.
- And we'll live forever.
Again.
- See the catch here?
- Bear Island...
- I see why Dragon King sent me here.
- is so great.
We love...
- Why?
- Bear Island.
- They say no one's ever left.
- Listen to the deity.
- Not because they don't want to.
- And we'll live forever.
- But because they can't.
- Bear Island is so great.
- This island cancels all power,
- We love Bear Island.
- and is guarded by these weirdos,
- Listen...
- so the Dragon King believed...
- to the deity.
- if lured here, I can never escape.
- And we'll live forever.
- Let alone take the Sea-Calming Pillar.
- Bear Island is so great.
- So...
- We love Bear Island.
- It's a trap?
- Listen to the deity.
- The Dragon King's trap for me.
- And we'll live forever.
- A trap for you?
- Bear Island is so great. We love...
- His scheme
- Listen to the deity.
- traps you here
- And we'll live forever.
even without me.
What am I doing here?
So I came here for nothing?
What was it all for?
What for?
Deep in this illusion,
we must stay steady in mind.
That's the true meaning of cultivation.
Right, Changshou?
Makes sense.
Mentor.
Changshou,
my hallucinations got worse.
Mentor.
It may not be an illusion.
Ling'e is truly here.
Mentor. Mentor.
Mentor.
It really is Ling'e.
Told you so.
It is Ling'e.
Mentor, thank you for waiting.
Ling'e.
Why are you alone?
Where is that little brat?
Mentor, rest assured.
Senior set this barrier.
I can break it.
Great.
Break.
Senior.
Help her out.
Sure.
Why?
Senior.
Ling'e.
Fairy Yunxiao is trapped
on the island by the Dragon King.
Once I report this to Celestial Court,
they'll set a blockade around.
Then I can make amends.
What happened?
Forgot I have no power here.
Going blindly without research.
A hard lesson. Never again.
No worries.
I can still swim out.
Why are you here?
I fish here every day.
Come to the beach, and you'll see me.
You here to fish too?
I'm here to slack off.
Were you trying to leave?
Such a wonderful place.
Just stay.
I will.
How could I leave this place?
Is this place
seriously impossible
to leave?
His scent
vanished right here.
No.
I must find you, sir.
To shatter dragon pride,
rebuild dragon glory,
and usher in a new era,
I shall become the light!
Light out.
Bear Island is so great.
Time to bathe, I can't wait.
Caught a fish upon my bait.
Eating full upon my plate.
Sorry, little fishy.
Are fish birthing humans now?
We'll go together tonight.
All right.
Why are you looking at me?
Nothing.
Yunxiao.
When do you plan to escape?
Why should I escape?
Do you intend...
This is
where Ancestral Witch heirs gather.
The Pregenesis Sword
is likely right here.
Without finding the sword,
I won't leave.
But that is...
Who?
Who changed my clothes?
Second Prince?
What?
Who changed my clothes?
Your enemy?
No, no.
Not that.
He...
Do not dwell on him.
Why not?
He's nuts.
These clothes...
Did you change me?
No.
Did he?
You changed me?
I prepared the clothes.
Is there a problem?
Of course there is.
These clothes...
Who put them on me?
You are a girl.
So a girl helped you change.
I am...
How can you tell I'm a girl?
You're slim and fair-featured.
Of course you're a girl.
I must teach you a thing or two.
Since I was little...
Men go to work,
and girls get to rest.
Since I was little,
I've been
a little girl.
What a pretty girl.
- Taste it.
- So pretty.
- Eat up.
- Have some more.
- Go ahead.
- Such a beauty.
Have some.
Have a bite.
Try some.
Give it a taste.
Such a pretty girl.
So lovely.
No thanks.
Who is it?
That is for slacking off.
No, no.
I was not slacking off.
I...
I grew tired from digging.
Just wanted a quick break.
Keep digging.
Dig less than three feet today,
no dinner for you.
That's right.
Do you really
have to dig?
Must it be done?
Don't.
No, wait.
I mean,
it must be done.
How could we not dig?
Exactly.
That's right.
How could we not dig?
Yes, yes.
Get to work.
Hurry up.
Go on.
Get up.
Start working.
Yes, yes.
Excuse me.
Grab your tools.
Bear Island rules.
The Human Clan is so fierce.
Labor is glorious.
- Bear Island rules.
- Dragon Clan must learn.
Hey, let me through.
Fresh fish soup.
Easy. Easy.
This should knock you out.
Then I can make my escape.
Ten times the dose.
Surely that'll finish you off.
I've never had
such delicious fish soup.
Right.
Never tasted soup this good.
Another bowl.
More.
All gone.
I'll make more tomorrow.
Here's one last drop.
Such a dose failed?
Frustrating.
Without power,
sleep won't reach Celestial Court.
I must find a way out.
Who are you?
New here?
Here to loaf around?
Sit.
Look at this scenery.
So beautiful.
This air.
So fresh.
Bear Island
is isolated from the world.
No strife.
What a paradise.
Seeing this scene,
poetry strikes me.
My friend.
Care to hear a verse?
The ocean vast
is all water and blue.
A little spider,
all legs right through.
Mortal humans
are nothing but jaw.
Come to Bear Island,
best place you saw.
When inspiration strikes,
I can't hold it back.
Next time,
make sure you do.
I am
Hua Ritian.
[Hua Ritian]
Cool name.
Ritian.
[*Sky-Breaker]
May I ask your name?
What were you doing just now?
I just saw the scenery
and painted a picture.
To be honest,
I am an artist.
Coming to Bear Island
was to pursue
the peak of art.
My friend,
if you're interested in art,
why not explore together
art's highest summit?
Where'd he go?
Something is off here.
Total lunatics.
A footprint?
Could it be Yunxiao?
Usually she flies in the sky.
Now she has come here,
and cannot hide her tracks yet.
So delicious.
Do you want it?
Then,
what'll you trade for it?
This is my favorite seashell.
No need.
Answer me one question.
Answer right,
and this fish is yours.
Okay, ask anything.
The Pregenesis Sword on this island.
Where is it?
A sword?
Meal's ready.
Time to eat.
Great.
Eat.
Let's go.
Dig in.
Not eating?
I have a sacred physique.
No need to eat.
A sacred physique?
What does that mean?
Means she's not hungry.
And...
You too?
I'm not hungry either.
But he must be starving.
You always eat the most.
Save us some.
Stop taking.
Have we met somewhere?
Uh...
I don't think so.
I know you.
No, you don't?
You're the human disciple
who sparred with me in Dragon Palace.
Am I right?
Yes. I remember now.
I forgot we sparred.
Shh. I'm here in disguise.
Keep it secret.
Okay, okay.
Same here.
No, thank you.
Say,
did you see a bearded man
in Dragon Palace?
A bearded man?
He's my savior.
What?
I came here to find him.
No big beards here.
Only little mustaches.
Try looking elsewhere?
He's not here.
That can't be.
I followed his scent
all the way here.
Dragons have sharp noses.
He's...
He can barely hold it.
Why not go help him?
Okay.
Yunxiao.
Sometimes,
I think you're pretty kind.
I can be unkind too.
You can stay kind.
Depends on my mood.
Alright.
Fruit is here.
Have some fruit.
The four of us met by chance.
Four strangers, with no ties.
Yet today we gather here.
I believe
it's the call of destiny.
So next, we shall face
even harder challenges.
I think we should be honest
and join hands.
Does he always talk like that?
Just being dramatic.
Well said, young lady.
Between us,
there should be no secrets.
Greetings.
I am Hua Ritian.
May I have your name, lady?
Ke Le'er.
We met by chance.
Your caution is only natural.
But as she said,
we should be honest
and join hands.
Fellow souls adrift...
Nice name.
What is yours?
Qing Luan.
I am Bai Shi.
So,
how do you know each other?
What do you think?
If I call you friends,
there's an odd distance.
If I call you strangers,
yet you seem
so synchronized.
Strange, Ke Le'er?
Truly strange.
Feels like
siblings share no blood.
Old foes who clicked at first sight.
Strangers with unspoken trust.
Vengeful soulmates across the years.
You're a couple.
No.
Hey, where are you going?
Take me with you.
None of your business.
Get lost.
Wait up.
♪I dare to live my own way♪
Definitely a couple.
♪The stars smile at fireflies♪
♪Roaming the city with reckless courage♪
♪Just watching swordplay while drunk♪
♪And in dreams, I reign supreme♪
♪Who can ever♪
I heard
a sword is at the peak.
But that place is forbidden.
We wouldn't dare go.
You must not go either.
♪Let the answer be empty♪
♪A varied life♪
♪Lives within all these things♪
♪I drink in the oncoming breeze♪
♪The steadiest surge♪
♪I grasp the vast firmament♪
♪Karma never falls empty♪
♪Let the thoughts weigh♪
♪Fulfill the first wish♪
♪Unruly♪
♪A carefree smile♪
Forbidden Land?
There is no deity
in...
[There is no deity in this world]
Did you not see
the huge characters?
I did.
Thanks for not strangling me, I guess.
Listen to me.
That line on the stone,
you must never say it aloud.
Sounds so terrifying.
Why can't I say it?
You've been here for days now.
Haven't you noticed
this village
is kind of strange?
I do think it's strange.
Do you know why?
As for the reason behind it,
I do not know either.
But I can tell you
what I saw with my own eyes.
That year,
pursuing the peak of art,
I came to this island.
The island welcomed me soon,
and I found peace and joy here,
reaching a new realm of art.
However,
I never imagined
beneath its peaceful surface
lay a hidden, dark side.
I quit.
Digging like this every day...
What is it all for?
Xiong Datou.
What are you doing?
Shh.
All we do is dig.
What's it for exactly?
For the Deity, of course.
The Deity blesses us
and gives us a home.
We must repay him.
Nonsense.
- That's not true.
- Watch it.
Hold your tongue.
I entered the Forbidden Land.
He...
- The Forbidden Land?
- He went there?
That will anger the Deity.
You're all fooled.
No one is protecting us at all.
In there stands a stone stele,
saying there is no deity in this world.
No deity.
Xiong Datou, you're crazy. Stop lying.
Get down.
No deity.
Nonsense.
You're all fooled.
Stop the nonsense.
No deity at all.
Xiong Datou.
No deity.
Forgive us.
We beg for your forgiveness.
Show mercy.
You're all fooled.
Please, mercy.
It was our fault.
Take pity on us.
Have some mercy.
Spare our lives.
Forgive our sins.
He's gone.
Let's go.
Where is Xiong Datou?
Datou is gone.
Where's Datou?
We... we love Bear Island.
Bear Island is so great.
Listen to the deity.
And we'll live forever.
We love Bear Island.
Bear Island is so great.
- Listen to the deity.
- After that,
- the man was never seen again.
- And we'll live forever.
However,
a few days later,
when the tide came in,
it washed up
a severed arm,
still wearing
his clothes from that day.
Is someone over there?
Where?
Who's there?
Didn't you see?
Right there.
I see no one.
Scaring yourself
with your made-up story?
Not made-up.
It's all true.
Pathetic.
There's a bearded man over there.
Yunxiao.
Could you stop wandering off?
Why do you always care where I go?
The atmosphere on this island
is so eerie.
And you have no power.
You should be more careful.
Even without power,
I must find the Pregenesis Sword.
Yunxiao.
Your stubbornness
makes things tough for me.
What's it to you?
Why are you so set
on getting the Sea-Calming Pillar?
What lies beneath the Eye of the Sea?
- You can't just...
- Enough.
Negotiation over.
Yunxiao.
If you refuse to listen,
I won't be nice anymore.
You wouldn't dare.
Neither of us has power anyway.
Bring it on.
Oh yeah?
Fine then.
Ke Le'er.
Hold on.
What's up?
Found my savior for me?
You bet.
Well,
you see him every day.
He is...
He is Hua Ritian.
Think about it.
Just four outsiders.
Qing Luan is a girl.
Excluding yourself,
and you know my deal.
Who else could it be?
Hua Ritian.
Exactly.
Makes sense.
Wait, actually...
Actually, he's been hiding his identity.
That must be intentional.
Since he's your savior,
he definitely recognizes you.
So why pretend not to know you?
Means he's protecting you.
That makes total sense.
Think further.
If he had a fake beard...
With a beard, wouldn't he look closer?
- Seems so.
- Definitely looks closer.
So go find Hua Ritian.
Test him right away.
Okay.
Go find him.
Hurry.
Quick tongue, huh?
Fortunately.
Stop sniffing.
I bathe every day.
No body odor.
You admire the view here daily.
But the view here is
ordinary.
Ordinary?
Ordinary.
That's the point.
Ordinary
is where its beauty lies.
Every word you say
sounds so profound.
Even to the ends of the sea,
a true soulmate is rare to see.
If you want to leave someday,
I can show you better views.
Where to?
Hua.
Have you seen the Dragon Palace?
Dragon Palace?
Carved pillars, jade tiles,
decked in pearls and jewels.
Utterly lavish,
yet dark and dreary.
Not as open and free as here.
You really went there?
I've seen it.
Have you seen a dragon?
Summoning clouds and rain,
soaring in the skies,
arrogant and mighty,
yet trapped in the sea.
So true, Hua.
You really are...
I've seen
too much.
Way too much.
So,
you're so amazing.
Why stay on Bear Island?
Bear Island?
What's wrong with it?
This peaceful sanctuary
is so quiet and serene.
Doesn't it entrance you?
I've been to many scenic places.
Compared to those,
this is nothing.
What have you seen?
I...
Have you seen the world's creation?
Heaven and earth blended as one.
Vast without directions.
Have you seen 100,000 stars
destruct all at once?
Light illuminated everything,
then destroyed it all.
Have you seen reincarnation?
Seen hellish ghosts wailing?
Seen tragic partings
in the mortal world?
I have.
I've seen
too much.
Way too much.
Let me tell you,
in this world,
the rarest beauty
is being ordinary.
My savior.
You are my lifelong faith.
It is everything
right before your eyes.
[Forbidden Land]
Yunxiao's footprint.
Hope she never learns
to hide her tracks.
This is...
an Object-Seeking Talisman.
No power works on Bear Island,
why would someone burn a talisman?
[There is no deity in this world]
[Because...]
Today's rocks are hauled up.
Great Deity,
you can inspect anytime.
A local?
You've been digging for centuries.
When will you find it?
Telepathy.
We've done all we can.
Isn't power forbidden here?
Great Deity,
we'd never
dare neglect your orders.
Then keep digging.
Dig another few centuries.
I believe
the Pregenesis Sword will show.
Someone else is hunting the sword?
This is
a formation?
Check it for me.
How long until the Great Tribulation?
Thirty years remain.
Thirty years.
Sword appears
and opens the Eye of the Sea,
triggering Great Tribulation.
Even if Fairy Yunxiao fails,
others will grab the Pregenesis Sword.
In that case,
the only way to break this
is to obtain the Pregenesis Sword
before anyone else.
♪See mortal joys and sorrows♪
♪Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds♪
♪Alas, love has many twists and turns♪
♪Memories filled with sorrow♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tearfully,
this life's bond is not over♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪
♪Down a few more cups of wine♪
♪Through land and sea,
I ask you to come♪
♪For honor's sake, upright and grand♪
♪Alas, our story is short♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tearfully,
this life's bond is not over♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪